{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "44 + 18",
      "answer": 62
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 54",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 45",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 76",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 62",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 38",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 18",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 70",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 68",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 19",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "18 + 72",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 63",
      "answer": 160
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 5",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 52",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 91",
      "answer": 184
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 8",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 21",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 45",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "75 + 74",
      "answer": 149
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 79",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 61",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 85",
      "answer": 146
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 64",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 52",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 73",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 29",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 1",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 61",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 69",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 27",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 44",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 87",
      "answer": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "89 + 13",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 28",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 44",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 10",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 78",
      "answer": 113
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 46",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 76",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 95",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 71",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 46",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 39",
      "answer": 138,
      "test": {
        "q": "What is the capital city of Poland?",
        "a": "???"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 4",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 74",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 40",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 92",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 38",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 75",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 4",
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 48",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 72",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 14",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 53",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 51",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 27",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "79 + 95",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 76",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 56",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 36",
      "answer": 46
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 47",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 71",
      "answer": 154
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 78",
      "answer": 169
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 67",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 11",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 54",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 52",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 74",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 34",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 63",
      "answer": 101,
      "test": {
        "q": "What is the capital city of France?",
        "a": "???"
      }
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 38",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 26",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 87",
      "answer": 167
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 19",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "34 + 46",
      "answer": 80
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 30",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 47",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 58",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 74",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 42",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 95",
      "answer": 188
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 19",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 78",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 6",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 44",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 62",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 85",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 7",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 64",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 36",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 10",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 81",
      "answer": 137
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 67",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 95",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 54",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 100",
      "answer": 181
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 68",
      "answer": 152
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 85",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 97",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 80",
      "answer": 96
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 1,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 0,
      "to": 100
    }
  }
}